vietnetcenter.com 2002-08-02

# VietNetCenter! Privacy Statement - Vietnamese Network Center - Viet Web Index, Viet Entertainment & Viet Search Engine for Vietnamese Communities and Vietnamese around the world. You also can search for Airline Tickets, Air fares, Air Ticket, Hotel Reser

**Overview**  
In general, using our site as a site visitor may be considered anonymous: we do not engage in any activity that will personally identify our site visitors.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, and to refine our site based on which features people use most often. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

 **Public Forums  **

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

 **Children's Guidelines  **

We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children: 

 We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent. 

We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent. 

When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to: Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes. 

Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification. 

Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity. 

We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any activity, game, or service. 

We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child. 

We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected. 

We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are unsuitable for children. 

We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online. 

Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: [info@vietnetcenter.com](mailto:info@vietnetcenter.com)

**Delete/Deactivate**  
This site gives users the following option for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service: To delete your record from our database, send us an email.

**IP Address**  
Each computer connected the Internet has a unique Internet Protocol (IP) Address, usually represented by a string of numbers separated by periods (for example, 255.255.255.255). Depending on how you connect to the Internet, you may have the same IP Address every time you connect, or your IP Address may change periodically. Most Internet service providers assign IP Addresses dynamically, meaning that your address is likely to change each time you connect to the Internet. Corporate networks often assign fixed IP Addresses, meaning your address may always be the same.

Your IP Address usually contains information that allows a Web server to tell who your Internet service provider is, or the name of your company if you're connecting from a corporate network. In some cases, an IP Address may also contain more information about your identity, especially if you are on a corporate network that assigns fixed IP Addresses. For more information, you should contact your Internet service provider or corporate network administrator.
